Nikita Jevdokiškin

Worker at your company



nikita.jevdokishkin@gmail.com +372 58367566 Tallinn, Estonia

About Me

I am 29 years old.

I don't sit still and am always looking for something new. I travel often and for a long time. Because of this, I changed many employers.

Skills?

B-category License (since 2016)

Understanding of Logistics

Web Design (Figma, HTML, CSS, Photoshop, AI, and more)

Some Cheap Ways to Travel.

Languages

Russian (native)

English

Estonian (not perfect, But I can understand)

Social

youtube.com/@ErieIn

t.me/erieln

EDUCATION

School

Tallinna 53 Keskkool

2002 - 2014, Tallinn

UNI

Estonian Academy of Arts

2016 - 2017, Tallinn

I was disappointed in the level of design that is taught at this university and I started my career as a designer on my own, so I studied for less than one year.

EXPERIENCE

Shift Supervisor

Maxima Eesti OÜ

Oct 2014 - Mar 2016- 1,5 year, Tallinn

Control of work and employees. Solution of logistics.

Logistician

Sanitex OÜ

Mar 2016 - Aug 2016 - 0,5 years, Tallinn

Ordering goods, sending goods. Logistics tasks.

Deputy Store Director

Maxima Eesti OÜ

Mar 2017 - Feb 2018 - 1 year, Tallinn

Control of store operations, logistics tasks.

Deputy Store Director

Araxes OÜ

May 2018 - May 2019 - 1 year, Tallinn

Control of store operations, logistics tasks.

Customers Service for Partners at Booking.com

Majorel Estonia OÜ

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020 - 0,5 year, Tallinn

Assistance to partners and hotels in management and financial transactions.

Freelance Web and UI Designer

Self-employed

2020 - until now - 4 years, Tallinn

I found myself on a new path. More like a hobby.

Security

Skarabeus Julgestusteenistus OÜ

May 2021 - Nov 2021 - 0,5 year, Tallinn

Inspection of territories, car trips between objects.

Master Technologist and Design

Mivar-Textile OÜ

Dec 2021 - Dec 2023 - 2 years, Tallinn

Design and production of home upholstered furniture.